Guide to the Boone and Crockett Club Records circa 1885-2009
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana-Missoula
- Conservation, 1902-2001; Series II; 21.5 linear feet
  - Conservation Committee, 1933-2001; Subseries 2; 17.875 linear feet
    - Conservation Grants Program - 2011 Additions, 1973-2001; Sub-subseries 2.1; 7.5 linear feet
      - Use by Deer and Pronghorn of Revegetated Coal Strip-Mines in the Northern Great Plains, J. Richard Medcraft, *RESTRICTED*, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 242/7)
      - Winter Relationships of Mosse to Oil and Gas Development in the Overthrust Belt, Wyoming, Lorrain Triest Rudd, *RESTRICTED*, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 243/1)
      - Desert Bighorn Ecology, Gary D. Miller, *RESTRICTED*, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 243/2)
      - Reppellents and Deterrents for Grizzly and Black Bears, Martin E. Smith, *RESTRICTED*, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 243/3)
      - Adaptation of Prohnhorn Following Reclocation, Audrey E. Goldsmith, *RESTRICTED*, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 243/4-5)
      - The Ecology of the Bobcat in the River of No Return Wilderness, Gary Mark Koehler, *RESTRICTED*, 1983-1988 (Box-folder 243/6)
      - Conservation Grants, Donations, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 234/12)
      - Ecology and Productivity of Two Eastern Sierra Deer Herds, Thomas E. Kucera, *RESTRICTED*, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 243/7)
      - Upper Yellowstone Valley Wild Sheep, Lynn R. Irby, *RESTRICTED*, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 243/8)
      - 4-H Workshop, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 234/13)
      - Habitat Alterations and Human Disturbance: Thier Impact on Mountain Lions in Southwestern Oregon, *RESTRICTED*, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 243/9)
      - Conservation Grants, Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 234/14)
      - Dominance Spacing Mechanisms and Population Regulation in Mountain Goats, Mark Masteller, *RESTRICTED*, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 243/10-11)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 234/15)
      - The Recovery of the Endangered Ocelot in Texas, Michael E. Tewes, *RESTRICTED*, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 244/1)
      - Elk Monitoring Project, *RESTRICTED*, 1987 (Box-folder 244/2)
      - "Ecology and Population Dynamics of Mule Deer in the Eastern Sierra Nevada, California", by Thomas Edward Kucera, 1988 (Box-folder 235/1)
      - Flathead Grizzly Project, 1988 (Box-folder 235/2)
      - Bighorn Sheep of Battlement Mesa, Mary L. Cunningham, *RESTRICTED*, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 244/3)
      - Bull Elk in the Blackfoot Drainage of Western Montana, *RESTRICTED*, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 244/4-5)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 235/3)
      - "A Description of the Major Plant Communities on the Theodore Roosevelt Memorial Ranch", by Russell James Offerdahl, 1989 (Box-folder 235/4)
      - Encampment River Bighorn Sheep Study, *RESTRICTED*, 1989 (Box-folder 244/6)
      - Craighead Wildlife-Wildlands Institute, Bighorn Sheep Research, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 235/5)
      - Desert Mule Deer Behaviors, *RESTRICTED*, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 244/7)
      - Desert-Dwelling Sheep, Vernon Bleich, *RESTRICTED*, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 244/8)
      - Grizzly and Black Bear Resource Partition, *RESTRICTED*, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 244/9)
      - Mule Deer Sexual Segregation, *RESTRICTED*, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 244/10)
      - Muskox Study, *RESTRICTED*, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 244/11)
      - Winter Foraging Ecology of Dall Sheep in the Brooks Range, Alaska, Michael C. Hansen,*RESTRICTED*, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 244/12)
      - Wolf-Moose Ecology on Isle Royale, *RESTRICTED*, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 244/13)
      - Conservation Grants, Reports, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 235/6)
      - Aspen Management for Big Game, Jill Anderson, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 245/1-2)
      - Elk Monitoring Project, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 235/7)
      - Grizzly and Black Bear Censusing, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 245/3)
      - Mountain Sheep Conservation of Genetic Resources, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 245/4)
      - Mule Deer Sexual Segregation, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 245/5)
      - Muskox Genetic Diversity, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 245/6)
      - Movement and Food Habits of Recolonizing Wolves, Seth Diamond, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 245/7)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 235/8)
      - Conservation Grants, Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 236/1)
      - Mountain Sheep Habitat, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 245/8-9)
      - Wolves Along the Rocky Mountain Front, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 246/1)
      - Mountain Sheep Helicopter Surveys, *RESTRICTED*, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 246/2)
      - Moose on Copper River Delta, Alaska, *RESTRICTED*, 1991 (Box-folder 246/3)
      - Population Dynamics and Habitat Use of Desert Mule Deer in the Trans Pecos Region, Richard K. Lawrence, 1991 (Box-folder 236/2)
      - Rocky Mountain Bighorn Sheep in South Central Wyoming, 1991 (Box-folder 236/3)
      - Alaskan Brown Bears, Population Genetics, *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 246/4)
      - Elk Monitoring Project, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 236/4)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 236/5)
      - Rocky Mountain Sheep, Conservation of Genetic Resources, *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 246/5)
      - Wolf Protection in Jasper National Park, Alberta, *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 246/6)
      - Cougar/Prey Relationships, *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 246/7)
      - Muskox Genetic Variation, *RESTRICTED*, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 246/8)
      - Flathead Grizzly Project, 1992 (Box-folder 236/6)
      - Kucera, Thomas E., Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 236/7)
      - Kodiak Brown Bear Research and Habitat Maintenance Trust, 1992 (Box-folder 236/8)
      - Wolf on Isyle Royale National Park, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 236/9)
      - Big Game and Nongame Birds, Effects of Aspen Management, Gail M. Turchi, *RESTRICTED*, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 247/1-2)
      - Black Bear Cub Mortality in New Mexico, *RESTRICTED*, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 247/3)
      - Alaskan Brown Bears, Molecular Population Genetics, *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box-folder 247/4)
      - Mountain Lion Ecology in Idaho, *RESTRICTED*, 1993 (Box-folder 247/5)
      - Black Bear Ecology of the Mississippi Alluvial Valley, *RESTRICTED*, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 247/6)
      - New Mexico Black Bear Project, Hornocker Wildlife Institute, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 236/10)
      - Polar Bear and Cub Research, *RESTRICTED*, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 247/7)
      - Moose Population Genetics, *RESTRICTED*, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 248/1)
      - "Advantages of Habitat Selection and Sexual Segregation in Mule and White-Tailed Deer", by Martin B. Main, 1994 (Box-folder 236/11)
      - "Summer-Fall Ecology of the Blackfoot-Clearwater Elk Herd of Western Montana", by Mark H. Hurley, 1994 (Box-folder 236/12)
      - Black Bear Habitat in Oregon, 1994 (Box-folder 237/1)
      - Mountain Sheep Horn and Skull Variation, *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box-folder 248/2)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, 1994 (Box-folder 237/2)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, Donor Report, 1994 (Box-folder 237/3)
      - Public Deer Hunting on Lands of the Smithsonian Environmental Research Center, 1994 (Box-folder 237/4)
      - Theodore Roosevelt Memorial Ranch, Evaluation of Mule Deer Hunting, *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box-folder 248/3)
      - Wolf Recolonization Along Montana's Rocky Mountain Front, *RESTRICTED*, 1994 (Box-folder 248/4)
      - Mountain Lion In the South Texas Plains, *RESTRICTED*, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 248/5)
      - Bighorn Sheep, Subspecies and Genetically Distinct Populations, *RESTRICTED*, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 248/6)
      - Elk Vulnerability to Hunter Harvest, *RESTRICTED*, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 248/7)
      - Identifying Lanscapes that Increase Elk Vulnerability, *RESTRICTED*, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 248/8)
      - Ecological Studies of Wolves on Isle Royale, *RESTRICTED*, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 249/1)
      - "A Multi-scale Behavioral Approach to Understanding the Movements of Woodland Caribou", By Chris J. Johnson, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 237/5)
      - Carnivore Community of Tropical Dry Forestes in Mexico, *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box-folder 249/2)
      - Conservation Grants, Award List, 1995 (Box-folder 237/6)
      - Muskoxen in the Northwestern Territories, *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box-folder 249/3-5)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, 1995 (Box-folder 237/7)
      - New Mexico Black Bear Project, Hornocker Wildlife Institute, 1995 (Box-folder 237/8)
      - Polar Bear Behavior, *RESTRICTED*, 1995 (Box-folder 249/6)
      - A Morphometric Reanalysis of Horn and Skull Variation in Mountain Sheep, Rob Roy Ramey, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 249/7)
      - Bighorn Sheep Habitat in the Rocky Mountain East Front, Montana, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 249/8)
      - Ecology of Wolves on the Copper River Delta, Alaska, John C. Carnes, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 250/1)
      - Effects of Large Herbivore Hunting Schemes on Cohabitant Ungulates, Wayne C. Van Zwoll, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 250/2-3)
      - Identifying Lanscapes that Increase Elk Vulnerability, C. Les Marcum and L. Jack Lyon, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 250/4)
      - National Fish and Wildlife Foundation, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 237/9)
      - White-Tailed Deer and Cattle, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 250/5-6)
      - Grants-in-Aid Subcommittee, Application Review Materials, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 237/10)
      - White-Tailed Deer, Behavior and Habitat-Use Patterns, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 251/1)
      - Desert Bighorn Sheep Populations, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 251/2)
      - Urban Deer in California, *RESTRICTED*, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 251/3)
      - "Identifying Landscape Elements in Relation to Elk Kill Sites in Western Montana", by Keith T. Weber, 1996 (Box-folder 237/11)
      - "Muskoxen/Sedge Meadow Interactions, North-Central Banks Island, Northwest Territories, Canada", by David L. Smith, 1996 (Box-folder 238/1)
      - National 4-H Shooting Sports Program, 1996 (Box-folder 238/2)
      - "Black Bear Ecology in Forested Wetlands of the Mississippi Alluvial Valley", by Thomas Hobart White, Jr., 1996-1997 (Box-folder 238/3)
      - Conservation of Woodland Caribou: Habitat Management Considerations at Landscape and Stand Levels in North-Central British Columbia, Chris J. Johnson, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 251/4)
      - Factors Affecting the Distribution and Abundance of Cougars in Montana, Shawn J. Riley, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 251/5)
      - Revision of Field Manual of Wildlife Diseases in Southeastern United States, Victor F. Nettles, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 251/6)
      - Geographic Information Systems to Examine Occurance of Record Class White-Tailed Deer, Larry Marchinton, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 251/7)
      - The Factors Affecting the Distribution and Abundance of Cougars in Montana, Shawn J. Riley, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 251/8)
      - Grizzly Bear Population Viability Analysis Based on Habitat, Mark S. Boyce, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 251/9)
      - Craighead Wildlife-Wildlands Institute, Bighorn Sheep Research, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 251/10)
      - The Conservation and Management of the Carnivore Community of Tropical Dry Forest in Mexico, C.A. Lopez-Gonzalez, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 251/11 (1 of 2))
      - The Conservation and Management of the Carnivore Community of Tropical Dry Forest in Mexico, C.A. Lopez-Gonzalez, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 252/1 (2 of 2))
      - The Study of Hunting, Fishing and Habitat Protection: Culture and the Political Economy of Conservation, John A. Baden, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 238/4)
      - The Suitability of Urban Areas as Migratory Mule Deer Winter Range, Mark F. McClure, *RESTRICTED*, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 252/2)
      - Identifying Landscapes That Increase Elk Vulberabillity, C. Les Marcum and L. Jack Lyon, *RESTRICTED*, 1997 (Box-folder 252/3)
      - Predation and Wild Turkey, Georgre Hurst, 1997 (Box-folder 238/5)
      - "Ecology of a Mountain Lion Population in Southern Texas", by Louis A. Harveson, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 238/6)
      - Collaborating and Communicating with Hunters, Farmers, and Biologists to Reduce Deer Damage to Agricultural Crops, Kathryn Reis, *RESTRICTED*, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 252/4)
      - Feasibility of Reintroduction of the Black Bear in to Mississippi, Jacob Bowman, *RESTRICTED*, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 252/5)
      - Habitat Relationships of Migratory Deer on Urban Winter Ranges, Marc F. McClure, *RESTRICTED*, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 252/6)
      - Chamberlain Creek Elk Studies, Final Report, 1998 (Box-folder 239/1)
      - "An Assessment of Habitat Suitability and Human Attitudes for Black Bear Restoration in Mississippi", by Jacob Lee Bowman, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 239/2)
      - Organochlorine Dynamics in Free-Ranging Polar Bears and Their Cubs, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 239/3)
      - "Habitat Evaluation and Communication Strategies to Reduce Agricultural Crop Damage by White-Tailed Deer", by Kathryn B. Reis, 2000 (Box-folder 239/4)
      - "Energy, Fractal Movement Patterns and Scale Dependent Habitat Relationship of Urban and Rural Mule Deer", by Mark F. McClure, 2001-2001 (Box-folder 239/5)
    - Conferences, Workshops and Collaborations, 1958-2000; Sub-subseries 3; 2.0 linear feet
      This sub-subseries documents the development of Boone and Crockett conservation workshops of the 1970s. This sub-subseries demonstrates the Club’s national and international involvement and collaboration in conservation. Of particular interest in this sub-subseries are materials documenting the Club’s involvement in the National Forest System Centennial Celebration and the National Wildlife Conservation Partners Summit that was hosted by the Club.
      - 1978 Boone and Crockett Wildlife Conservation Workshop, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 101/7)
      - 38th North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, The Committee on North American Wildlife Policy, Report, 1973 (Box-folder 101/8)
      - 57th North American Wildlife and Natural Resource Conference, Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 101/9)
      - American Committee for International Conservation, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 101/10)
      - American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 101/11)
      - North American Black Bear Workshop, Correspondence, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 102/1)
      - North American Black Bear Workshop, Invoices, Receipts, and Statements, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 102/2)
      - Browne Memorial Cabin, Mount McKinley National Park, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 102/3)
      - Citizens Committee on Natural Resources, Correspondence, 1962 (Box-folder 102/4)
      - Coalition for Hunting and Wildlife Management, 1990 (Box-folder 102/5)
      - Cooperative Projects, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 102/6)
      - Dallas Safari Club, Annual Organizational Materials, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 102/7)
      - Dallas Safari Club, Annual Organizational Materials, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 102/8)
      - Dallas Safari Club, Membership List, 1988 (Box-folder 102/9)
      - Earthcare Conference, 1975 (Box-folder 102/10)
      - Earthcare Project, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 102/11)
      - International Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies, Communications Committee, 1991 (Box-folder 102/12)
      - International Conference on Wildlife Biotelemetry, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 102/13)
      - International Council for Game and Wildlife Conservation, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1976 (Box-folder 102/14)
      - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 102/15)
      - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources, 1961-1975 (Box-folder 102/16)
      - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources, 1966-1981 (Box-folder 102/17)
      - International Union for Conservation of Nature and Natural Resources, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 103/1-2)
      - The Interparliamentary Conference on the Global Environment, 1990 (Box-folder 103/3)
      - Missouri Sport Shooting Clinic, 1971 (Box-folder 103/4)
      - National Coalition for Nongame Fish and Wildlife Conservation, 1977 (Box-folder 103/5)
      - National Forest System Centennial Celebration, 1991 (Box-folder 103/6-7)
      - National Forest System Centennial Celebration, American Forestry Association, Correspondence, 1991 (Box-folder 103/8)
      - National Forest System Centennial Celebration, Banquet, 1991 (Box-folder 103/9)
      - National Forest System Centennial Celebration, Collection Agreement Between The Boone and Crockett Club and The United States Department of Agriculture, Forest Service, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 103/10)
      - National Forest System Centennial Celebration, Invitations, 1991 (Box-folder 103/11)
      - National Forest System Centennial Celebration, Poster Competition, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 103/12)
      - National Forest System Centennial in Cody, Wyoming and Washington D.C., Proposal for Celebrations, 1991 (Box-folder 103/13)
      - National Legislative Action Council, 1977 (Box-folder 103/14)
      - National Wildlife Conservation Partners Summit, Facilitator Materials, 2000 (Box-folder 104/1)
      - National Wildlife Conservation Partners Summit, Meeting Packet, 2000 (Box-folder 104/2)
      - National Wildlife Conservation Partners Summit, Dan Pedrotti, Opening Speech, 2000 (Box-folder 104/3)
      - National Wildlife Conservation Partners Summit, Planning Materials, 2000 (Box-folder 104/4)
      - Natural Resources Council Of America, 1977 (Box-folder 104/5)
      - Natural Resources Council of America, 4th Annual Conservation Community Banquet, 1988 (Box-folder 104/6)
      - Natural Resources Council of America, Membership List, 1984 (Box-folder 104/7)
      - North American Whitetail Conference, 1982 (Box-folder 104/8)
      - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, Schedule, 1973 (Box-folder 104/9)
      - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, 1981 (Box-folder 104/10)
      - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 104/11)
      - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, Correspondence, 1990 (Box-folder 104/12)
      - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, 1991 (Box-folder 104/13)
      - Northern Wild Sheep Council, Conference, 1978 (Box-folder 104/14)
      - The Renewable Natural Resources Foundation, 1980 (Box-folder 104/15)
      - Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation Show, Booth, 1992 (Box-folder 104/16)
      - Rocky Mountain Elk Foundation, Annual Elk Camp and Exposition, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 104/17)
      - Southeastern Association of Fish and Wildlife Agencies, Legal Writing Competition, 1991 (Box-folder 104/18)
      - Wild Sheep Workshop, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 104/19-20)
      - Wildlife Congress, 1996 (Box-folder 105/1)
      - Wildlife Conservation Workshop, Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 105/2)
      - Wildlife Conservation Workshop, Survey on Proposal, 1975 (Box-folder 105/3)
      - Wildlife Legislative Fund of America, Correspondence, Memoranda, and Reports, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 105/4)
      - Wildlife Management Institute, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 105/5)
      - Workshops, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 105/6)
    - Subject Files and Miscellaneous, 1947-2000; Sub-subseries 4; 0.75 linear feet
      This sub-subseries contains articles, clippings, correspondence, and additional materials.
      - Alaska Conservation Society, News Bulletins, 1965 (Box-folder 105/7)
      - Alaska Professional Hunters Association, undated (Box-folder 105/8)
      - Articles, Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box-folder 105/9)
      - Big Game Refuge Areas, 1948-1961 (Box-folder 105/10)
      - Miscellaneous Bulletins, 1947-1960 (Box-folder 105/11)
      - Bureau of Land Management, Grazing Fees, 1978 (Box-folder 105/12)
      - California Desert Bighorn, 1973 (Box-folder 105/13)
      - Cape Cod National Seashore, National Park Service Proposal, 1959 (Box-folder 105/14)
      - Eastern Timber Wolf, 1975 (Box-folder 106/1)
      - Echo Park Dam, 1955 (Box-folder 240/1)
      - Effects of the 1990 Farm Bill on Fish and Wildlife, by Anne E. Kinsinger, 1991 (Box-folder 106/2)
      - Exotic Game Animals, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 106/3)
      - Federation for North American Wild Sheep, 1990 (Box-folder 106/4)
      - Foundation for Research on Economics and the Environment, 1988 (Box-folder 106/5)
      - History of the Committee on Conservation of Forests and Wildlife of the Camp Fire Club of America, 1956-1988 (Box-folder 106/6)
      - Kodiak National Wildlife Refuge, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 106/7)
      - Marias Pass Grizzly Bear Interpretive Trail, 1994 (Box-folder 106/8)
      - National Park System, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 106/9)
      - National Park System, 1991 (Box-folder 106/10)
      - People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals, Articles, 1991 (Box-folder 106/11)
      - Roosevelt National Park, Map of Proposed Designation, undated (Box-folder 106/12)
      - Carl Rungius, Article, undated (Box-folder 106/13)
      - Theodore Roosevelt Memorial, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 106/1)
      - United States Department of the Interior, Annual Reports, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 106/15)
      - Western Foundation for Raptor Conservation, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 106/16)
      - Wildlife Legislative Fund of America, Newsletter, 1990 (Box-folder 106/17)
      - World Wildlife Fund, Bulletins, 1966 (Box-folder 106/18)
      - World Wildlife Fund, Game Conservation Report, 1963 (Box-folder 106/19)
  - Fair Chase and Other Positions, 1959-2001; Subseries 3; 1.0 linear foot
    The idea of fair chase was first proposed by Theodore Roosevelt and was present in the original Club constitution. It prohibited “killing bear or cougar in traps, crusting moose, elk or deer in deep snow, jacking, or killing them from a boat.” This subseries documents the evolution of the Club’s Fair Chase policy from the early 1960s through the late 1990s.
    This subseries also includes materials related to the Club’s positions on a wide variety of topics from gun control, private property rights, and animal rights to the reintroduction of the wolf in Yellowstone National Park. Researchers will find materials documenting the development of these positions as well as responses from Club members to the Club’s position papers.
    - Alliance for the Wild Rockies, Senator Max Baucus Wilderness Bill, 1994 (Box-folder 107/1)
    - Allocation of Alaska D2 Lands, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 107/2)
    - Endangered Species Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 107/3)
    - Fair Chase and Related Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 107/4)
    - Fair Chase Policy, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 107/5)
    - Fair Chase Policy, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1960-1974 (Box-folder 240/2)
    - Fair Chase Policy, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 107/6)
    - Fair Chase Policy Revision, 1975 (Box-folder 107/7)
    - Fair Chase Policy Statements, 1990 (Box-folder 107/8)
    - Fair Chase Principles, Correspondence, 1994 (Box-folder 107/9-11)
    - Fair Chase Questions, 1987 (Box-folder 107/12)
    - Fair Chase Statements, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 107/13)
    - Fair Chase Statement, Revisions, Correspondence and Memoranda, 1998 (Box-folder 107/14)
    - Firearm Legislation, 1959 (Box-folder 107/15)
    - Firearms Legislation, Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 107/16-17)
    - Grizzly Bear Position Paper, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 108/1)
    - Gun and Rifle Registration, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 108/2)